Tufts Nutrition UP036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Nutrition
1985 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
Publications
UP036
0.75 Linear Feet
1 Volumes
12 Digital Object(s)
64.6 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains a Newsletter of Nutrition Science and Policy at Tufts University for Alumni and Alumnae. Tufts Nutrition is published twice a year. It was formerly entitled "News for Alumni and Alumnae."
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Publications is one of four departments comprising Tufts Office of Communications. This Office is responsible producing magazines, newsletters, and marketing material for Tufts University. Through design and writing the Office of Publication aims to capture and share the visual and intellectual identity of the University. The Office also offers editorial, design, and project management services for Tufts departments, and maintains external contracts with photographers and design firms.
- Tufts Nutrition, 1985 -- 2019; UP036.001; 0.75 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 12 Digital Object(s); 64.6 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a Newsletter of Nutrition Science and Policy at Tufts University. For Alumni and Alumnae. Formerly "News for Alumni and Alumnae."
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - News For Alumni and Alumnae School of Nutrition, 1985 -- 1987; UP036.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    November 1985, December 1986, and Fall 1987
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 1997; UP036.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 1998; UP036.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 1999; UP036.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 1999; UP036.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 1999; UP036.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2000; UP036.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2000; UP036.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2001; UP036.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2001; UP036.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2002; UP036.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    Accessed and printed from http://nutrition.tufts.edu/docs/pdf/magazine/nutMAGspring02.pdf on February 19, 2008
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2002; UP036.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2003; UP036.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2003; UP036.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2004; UP036.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2004; UP036.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    Volume, issue
    6, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2005; UP036.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    6, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2005; UP036.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    7, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2006; UP036.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    7, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2006; UP036.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    8, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition Spring, 2007; UP036.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    8, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2007; UP036.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    9, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2008; UP036.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    9, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2008; UP036.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    Second copy in bound volume in Reading Room.
    10, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2009; UP036.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    10, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Fall, 2009; UP036.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
    11, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Spring, 2010; UP036.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    11, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2010; UP036.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
    12, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2011; UP036.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    12, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2012; UP036.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    13, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter 2012 -- Summer 2015; UP036.001.004.00001; 1 Volumes (Volume 4)
    Volume, Number
    Volume 12, no. 1 -- Volume 16, no. 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2012; UP036.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    13, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2013; UP036.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
    14, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2013; UP036.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
    14, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2014; UP036.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
    15, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2014; UP036.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
    15, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2015; UP036.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2015; UP036.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2016; UP036.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
    17, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2016; UP036.001.003.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    17, 2
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2017; UP036.001.003.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 29)
    18, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2017; UP036.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2018; UP036.001.003.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 30)
    19, 1
  - Tufts Nutrition, Summer, 2018; UP036.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Nutrition, Winter, 2019; UP036.001.003.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 31)
    20, 1